Searching for Bobby D is a comedy film directed by Paul Borghese.
Four young filmmakers try to raise money for their project by telling potential
investors that Robert De Niro is on board -- now, they have to find him.
Johnny Argano, played by William DeMeo.
Matty, played by Matthew Ziff.
Louie, played by Paul Cicero.
Piscopo, played by Jack Bank.
Jerome, played by Tyson Beckford.
Sherri Dansen, played by Sandra Bernhard.
Joshua Waitzkin (born December 4, 1976) is an American former chess
player, martial arts world champion, and author.
As a child, he was recognized as a prodigy, and won the U.S.
Junior Chess championship in 1993 and 1994.
The film Searching for Bobby Fischer is based on his early life.
The tone is lighthearted.